http://www.electronicalarms.com/privacy-policy/

Electronic Alarms
Contact | Branch Info | Privacy Policy | Bill PayAlarm.com
Get In Touch! (401) 737.2221
HomeResidentialCommercialCommercial FireServicesAbout UsContact Us
Quality CraftsmanshipResources
10 Points for Choosing a Home Security Company 15 Point Checklist FAQ Careers NewsLinksCoverage Areas
Privacy Policy
We at Electronic Alarms are sensitive to the concerns of our clients and associates in regards of use of their personal information. Electronic Alarms gathers this information for the sole use of communicating with our clients. Under no circumstances will Electronic Alarms sell or distribute contact information that has been received through our website forms or any other means.
Cookies are used at a very basic level to obtain non-personal data, most visited pages for example, to help us re-evaluate our content to better serve our clients.
For further information or questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact:
Tel: 401-737-2221 Email: customerservice@electronicalarms.com
Coverage Areas
EA operates as division of American Alarm & Communications Inc and maintains a 24-hour service presence at their current Warwick RI location.
24 - Hour Customer Service
There are times when talking to a knowledgeable person by phone can fix a service problem. So we have technical staff on call 24 hours a day to respond to urgent customer questions.
Connections
Like Us On Facebook
© 2017 Electronic Alarms a division of American Alarm and Communications, Inc.
All services provided by Electronic Alarms are subject to the terms and conditions and limitations of our installation and monitoring contract(s).
